Hello friends, I am Pankaj Soni, and
I welcome you all to the Pankaj Tech YouTube channel.
If you're visiting our channel for the
first time, please
subscribe and
hit the bell button to receive notifications for all my videos. Please like
and share this video with your friends and
family so
everyone can benefit from it. In today's
video, we'll discuss the
fundamentals, technical targets, and futures of ICICI Lombard stock. We'll also
discuss its futures and options, where you can earn a significant
profit.
Through Hain Guru's website, you
can invest in stocks, mutual funds, fixed deposits, stock futures and options, gold, and more. It's
very easy to operate. You
can download the app on your Android phone
and trade on your laptop. The
website is very fast and simple, and
anyone can trade without any trading experience.
Through your desktop,
website, or app,
you can easily find 19 stocks
that you should buy or
sell.
If you have
n't opened your account yet, I've
seen the link for opening an account in the description.
You can easily open your account on Groww by clicking on that link.
Your account will open within 2 hours, and you'll be
able to invest. If you have any kind of
problem, you can comment on me, call me,
or WhatsApp me. I've provided my phone
number and mobile number
in the description box. You can get help from that. So,
today we'll discuss this stock, Fox.
It's
a very well-known stock in the insurance sector.
Today, it's Sunday,
January 6, 2012. The stock market
is closed for trading. The last price of this stock
is
100. The stock
closed at 3.25 on Friday,
and it has seen a rise of 1.98 in one day.
If we talk about one week, it has gained
4.73% in one week itself
and in one month it has generated excellent returns of
5.04%. In one year, it has given an amazing
return of 1.3%.
In serials, it has given an amazing return of
61.08% and in five years, By Das has
given an amazing return of 115.1% to its investors. This means that
in just five years, it has
more than doubled your investment.
If you had invested Rs 1 lakh in it five years ago,
you would have more than Rs 2 lakh today
or you would have Rs 2.5 lakh
if ​​you had booked a profit in it some time ago
because right now this stock has gained a lot.
Now let's also look at its technicals. Should
you invest in it now
or not? So let me
open its technical chart
and you will easily understand how
its technicals are.
So see, this stock is
trading above its day's average.  This
means you can invest in it for the long term right now.
Therefore, its 210 moving average is
108. So if you get it,
update it for some time. If it falls
now and you get this stock from one to z
here, then this will be your
best buy for the long term.
In the short term, it has the
support of a fixed moving average, so for the short term, you
can buy it right now. It is possible that it may
fall further, so you can add more quantity to it and
trade this press or
you
can make a good profit by adopting a buy only study.
If we talk about its performance, today's
low is
more than 100 paise and the suggested
value is 6 and it has
fallen a little below this suggested level. It could not reach the suggested level, but the
52-week low is
more than 100. As you can see, this stock has also
fallen well below the ravine
and is approaching its 52-week low.
So at this time you can invest in it for the long term
and even if the Yagya stock
falls, its fundamentals are strong and
you
can also buy it further by adopting the strategy of buy on dips.
In Lundkar, this stock will
give you good profits and is
trading at more than 100 times the open price, which is a free life volume of 8016. Now you
can exit profit booking in it at any time. I advise you to invest in such stocks
which are Nifty
stocks, they fluctuate in which your
chances of loss are very less.
Its value is active 438 crores, which has been done
today,
if we try to know what has been happening
in it, what are their thoughts
about this stock, then as you can see,
60% of the analysts are advising to like it,
50% are advising to make the analysis successful
and 25
percent at least are advising to sell it.  They are
advising to hold 50%,
so the overall rating in this is that the bikerni
is hesitant because most of the left is
advising to like it.
Protein Earlist has done its research in this topic, has
examined its fundamentals and technicals, only
after that, it is giving you this advice. Let us
discuss the fundamentals of Bhav Mirch,
how are the fundamentals, so
as you can see on the screen, its
market cap is
6030 crores, which turns out to be a large cap
company, and there is also another
company in which investing can be
beneficial for you at any time. In the long term,
its back is 2.57, which
proves to be an expensive stock
because the stocks which have more than p20 are
available at a team valuation
and such stocks are considered expensive,
their
price is expensive, then its price is
7.70, which means that this stock is
seven times more than its actual value than its antiquated value.  It is trading at
152. Look, the industry behind it is
29.75 points, but the price of such people is
32.57. From this you can know that the
stock of ICC Lombard is
creating a lot of profit on every person from its industries.
Its yield is like this, it has a yield of 21.32%,
which is a very good thing. If
the return on equity of any stock is
more than 100 percent, then its yield is
considered good. This proves the health of the stock. So,
Lombard is very good from the RO area. This yield is
27.57. The difference is also good. It is 0.5%.
Because it is a growth stock, hence it
prefers to give less profit. Its value is
108, its
book value is 108. Now let us
discuss its financials,
how are the financials,
what are the changes in the revenue, profit and network of Quarter of Water Inn,
we will discuss all that too.
So look at the revenue, the revenue was generated in September 2012.
12833 for dialogue
emphasis more than 300 in September 21 all the
features which are in focus and as you
can see quarter on quarter we are seeing
a good growth in the revenue of these
so this shows the financial help of the stock
well now let us see in the profit
how will the profit be quarter on
quarter so in September 2010 they
generated profit of 486 and all these
figures are given in ignite
but in this the copy which they made in
in read officer jun21 by
taking 19421 the requested profit
was
fors 57 let us also discuss the network of
cotton quarter how was their network
as you
can see in the graph right now that their network has
seen a good growth in turn on quarter and it is being seen
in it it was the network of white cement
from this 40
Jatin in jun21 800 to 1000 pocket
in September 2001 Nobel
087  797 So their network is
growing rapidly and they have made a record,
then the network is in the quarter of September 21,
now we will tell them and tell them how the
interviews were on the lips,
so there is a good increase in Ravindra as well, you must have
understood by seeing the bathroom that
they have generated good revenue,
friend, on air, so in 2017 they
generated
800 to 1000 in khao se z,
Praveen generated a record on 21 May, so it is
strong
and a good
increase is being seen in this, which shows their financial
help very well, we will
talk about how to make a profit and this
profit is air and clear, a
lot of increase is being seen in this as well, as
you must have understood by looking at the graph,
Q-17 generated no profit
in 73221 connected to 12920 in 2019,
take 2103 and this certificate is up and
now their network also  Let's talk about the
changes in the network.
By looking at their graph, you must have understood that their
network is also performing very well. In
2017, their network was
4 times faster and in 2018, it was
62,240,862 crore and in 2019, Jio's net worth
is growing very fast and
in 2019, they have
made a record.
We will know about this company,
how is their business, which businesses do they do,
you will get complete details. Stay tuned
in this video and listen to these things comfortably
and try to understand, only
after that you should take investment decision. So, the
company itself is like Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited, Digital India
Based General Insurance Company, so their
business is in India only. It is an India's
best general insurance
company. This company offers insurance coverage
for motors.
So, it is
very important for you to know which things they insure. So, the
company which offers insurance
coverage for motors, it does motor insurance and
health insurance.
Travel, Home, Student Travel and more.
It insures all these things. Its
segments include Cloud Fire,
Engineering, Marine Cargo, Marine Whole,
Motor Body, Motor Pay, Work, Musser Compensation,
Public Product Liability, Personal
Accident, Now Tuition, Health Credit Insurance,
Crop, Weather Insurance and other health
products. Products include Motor Insurance,
Two Wheeler Insurance, Health
Insurance, Complete Health Insurance, Health
Booster, Personal Accident Insurance,
International Travel Insurance, Home
Insurance, Mara in Insurance Business,
Third Party Insurance, Crop
Insurance. It also offers various services like
Grievance Redressal,
Retrieve Court Intimate Claim, Mara in
Property Claims, Live Chat and Renew
Policy. So, it is a very good subscriber.
Its service in the insurance sector is
very diversified.
Its parent organization
is registered in the name of Lombard General Insurance Company Limited. This company was started in
12:00 Star Plus and today it has
completed 21 years. Its Managing
Director is Mr. Bahar Das Gupta.
NSA symbol is ICICI General.  The
insurance is in someone else's name. Now,
for this, let's add its logo and add the Edison number.
This is it. Now let's see its shareholding
pattern, what is the Tasir pattern
and Motors has a very good holding in it.
It is set at 4828. For example, there is
27.01 meeting in it. He has
invested a good amount in it. Retainers
also have a good holding in his 15.57 meeting.
Keep the top important meetings
like the slot Banking and Finance
Services holding of 3.20 operation. This cut
Banking and Finance Services
holding of 2.7 percent. A specific Artist
Equity holding of 2.4 percent and
ICC President will only focus on
2.2.4% holding in it. Now we will
talk about some of its news events and films.
If I open its feature option,
as you can see, the
call in its option change is 38.65
percent and there is an
increase of 39.04 percent in it. Put Kajol in it.
Shampoo it is 33.50 and in this I have stream there
is a fall of 56.38 if you see its features then
this is the feature of feature 2017 Lido and its
rate is also poison from hands and there is an
increase of 2.02 percent in it
and
if you see the future of Bluetooth 4000 then it is
101 in this also there is an increase of 2.32 percent
and this is the feature of 31st March
till this feature is
discussed without Yorkshire Begusarai then one and a half
their board meeting is going to be held on 1972
that is the directors meeting
that they give a very good dividend,
you have given dividend thrice in a year on
0th October so one tweeted for rupees one
technical so one took a photo and gave dividend
and eight months twenty one and its difference
total both pieces have been done
that news is coming out of them it is also
important for you to know that like ICC Monday
represent 0.2 on St. Francis now a
little bit in this  There has been a decline in skin cases. ESI
Numbered has launched its initiative to help
flood-affected customers in Chennai. So, ESI has
taken some initiatives to help
flood-
affected
customers in Chennai. Law University has launched some initiatives for them in Chennai,
which is good
news. How to
make simple hole targets. Let's talk about
what the report is about these products. So,
as you can see, there is a more
intimate and initiatives coverage on ESI
long but with amazing stop games. So now you
know that Morgan
Stanley's research reports were very important
and the research report is
quite reliable and they have
given ICC Lombard a buy rating, due to which it
is currently doing well.
Let's now read their full report and
try to understand what they have
said in their report. And this is the
latest report
about the loot.
Shubhendu Sabha seats of ICC Lombard
General Insurance Company got after three days ago.
Morgan Stanley turned and waste
on the company setting on  Its long-term
potential. Tomars
were Morgan Stanley's
commentators on ICC Lombard General Insurance Company's long-term potential. It is an
extreme regional point in time to
build. Council's positive talk is
that in the next three months,
you will get an opportunity to
build your position in large-cap quality stocks.
Research house Saturn is not initiating
coverage on the general insurance sector
in rural areas. ICC Lombard is the largest
multi-line private sector player in
India with its track record of
profitability, diversification and risk
management. He said that this is a
flood stock. It is a player with a
very good and strong track record in the private sector, which
means its fundamentals are
very strong. There is strong
investor confidence about the
company's loss for lots of premium.
Market share has slowed down in recent times.
Direct premium growth is in single digits and this is a long-term
distance to benefit from the multi-
digit growth potential of the non-life
insurance industry. E M Organic Acid
Attacks Private Companies Market Share to
Rise from This One Per Cent  Into the versus then
15 per cent and child financial year
36th Guava-Guava Stanley believes that the
financial year at your will have a
possibility of 35 per cent growth in
this insurance sector, such a number
decoding to the not will see its growth,
direct premium growth bottom of December
21, 201 double digit in a quarter Indian
subject, double-digit growth is going to be achieved in this
Morgan Stanley has
set up a price target of 90, the
target that it has fixed for ICC is 100
subscribe and this
subscribe
closing and
at December 6 price, they can
take advantage of Morgan Stanley research, you
can invest in stocks and
can also earn huge profits, so
if you still have not subscribed to our channel, then
please subscribe our channel,
like,
comment and share
with your friends and family that and they
will meet in one next video
and finally thank you for watching the video, tell
about my video to your friends
so the  Can Benefit